{"Agathion": {"stats": [5, 5, 4, 7, 4], "skills": ["Zio"], "question": "Hey, let's play a game! Guess what I wanna eat!", "a": "Hamburgers", "b": "Curry", "c": "Shut up", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Chariot", "trait": "Odd Immunity", "inherits": "elec", "item": "Zio"}, "Andras": {"stats": [3, 6, 3, 6, 7], "skills": ["Bufu"], "question": "If you capture me, what you going to do to me?", "a": "Eat you in a hot pot", "b": "Take you to a taxidermist", "c": "You'll be my new stylish coat", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Devil", "trait": "Foul Contagion", "inherits": "ice", "item": "Evil Touch"}, "Angel": {"stats": [2, 11, 3, 5, 4], "skills": ["Kouha"], "question": "Hey. Aren't you hungry? Can we take a break and go eat somewhere?", "a": "Eat you in a hot pot", "b": "Take you to a taxidermist", "c": "You'll be my new stylish coat", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Justice", "trait": "Chained Technique", "inherits": "bless", "item": "Kouha"}, "Anubis": {"stats": [3, 9, 6, 3, 4], "skills": ["Megido"], "question": "Hey. So whaddya think when you think about the future?", "a": "An average level of happiness", "b": "Live fast, die young", "c": "I just want to enjoy the now", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Judgement", "trait": "Deadly Plague", "inherits": "almighty", "item": "Makouga"}, "Anzu": {"stats": [7, 2, 7, 4, 5], "skills": ["Garu"], "question": "Me am really in soup, now. Do what you want. Me am ready if you want grill me, so...", "a": "OK, I'll make you into soup", "b": "Fine I'll grill you", "c": "All right I'll mince you!", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Hierophant", "trait": "Wind Lineage", "inherits": "wind", "item": "Garula"}, "Apsaras": {"stats": [4, 9, 3, 4, 5], "skills": ["Bufu"], "question": "I wonder if us speaking together like this now means that we are somehow connected...", "a": "Eh, could be", "b": "No, I don't think so", "c": "It's what we call destiny", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Priestess", "trait": "Self Hypnosis", "inherits": "ice", "item": "Media"}, "Arahabaki": {"stats": [3, 5, 3, 7, 7], "skills": ["Marin Karin"], "question": "So why me in this situation right now? Why me at your mercy?", "a": "Times have changed", "b": "Humans are powerful", "c": "This is a difficult topic...", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Hermit", "trait": "Iron Immunity", "inherits": "ailment", "item": "Tapsuan"}, "Archangel": {"stats": [4, 4, 3, 7, 7], "skills": ["Kouha"], "question": "Do you seek friendly competition with a beloved neighbor? Or have you come to destroy a hated foe?", "a": "You're a beloved neighbor", "b": "You're a loathsome foe", "c": "You sound preachy", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Justice", "trait": "Chained Technique", "inherits": "bless", "item": "Hama"}, "Arsene": {"stats": [4, 3, 8, 3, 7], "skills": ["Eiha"], "question": "I am the rebel's soul that resides within you. If you so desire, I shall consider granting you the power to break through this crisis.", "a": "Give me your power", "b": "I don't want to die", "c": "...", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Fool", "trait": "Last Stand", "inherits": "curse", "item": "Arsene's Cane"}, "Baal": {"stats": [8, 6, 5, 2, 4], "skills": ["Garu"], "question": "As far as you're concerned, what kind of person was I to you?", "a": "My rival", "b": "Nobody, really", "c": "It doesn't matter", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Emperor", "trait": "Wind Lineage", "inherits": "wind", "item": "Yagrush"}, "Baphomet": {"stats": [2, 10, 5, 5, 3], "skills": ["Megido"], "question": "A bad rep spreads like wildfire. If I were you, I'd quit all this nonsense. What's the point?", "a": "You're right", "b": "I don't care", "c": "I don't know any other way", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Devil", "trait": "Burning Touch", "inherits": "almighty", "item": "Bufudyne"}, "Barong": {"stats": [6, 7, 5, 4, 3], "skills": ["Zio"], "question": "Ah, it's a shame. If I'd taken this seriously from the start, I wouldn't be in this sorry state", "a": "Then get serious now", "b": "Making excuses?", "c": "I wasn't trying either", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Emperor", "trait": "Bless Lineage", "inherits": "elec", "item": "Ziodyne"}, "Belphegor": {"stats": [10, 2, 7, 1, 5], "skills": ["Bufu"], "question": "Somethin' bad happen in yer life or somethin', sonny?", "a": "It's not like that", "b": "Nothing but bad things...", "c": "You're getting on my nerves!", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Tower", "trait": "Focused Gaze", "inherits": "ice", "item": "Mabufula"}, "Berith": {"stats": [5, 7, 7, 3, 3], "skills": ["Cleave"], "question": "What kinda fate do you think there is in this meetin' between me and you?", "a": "Fate brought us together", "b": "There is no such thing", "c": "I want to end this fate", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Hierophant", "trait": "Crisis Management", "inherits": "phys", "item": "Cleave"}, "Bicorn": {"stats": [2, 4, 7, 7, 5], "skills": ["Garu"], "question": "Know how they say, Be kind ta yer elders? Has no one ever taught you that?", "a": "Someone did once", "b": "I don't care", "c": "I don't want to grow old", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Hermit", "trait": "Heavyweight", "inherits": "wind", "item": "Lunge"}, "Black Ooze": {"stats": [7, 6, 4, 4, 4], "skills": ["Eiha"], "question": "They always give the guys katsudon! You got anything like that for me!?", "a": "Katsudon, coming right up", "b": "How about sushi...", "c": "I have nothing for you", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Moon", "trait": "Odd Immunity", "inherits": "curse", "item": "Headbutt"}, "Cerberus": {"stats": [7, 4, 3, 5, 6], "skills": ["Agi"], "question": "You go back to your mother' arms. You need take nap now", "a": "I'm not that young", "b": "I'm not sleepy yet", "c": "Mom will wait till I'm done", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Chariot", "trait": "Fire Lineage", "inherits": "fire", "item": "Megaton Raid"}, "Chernobog": {"stats": [4, 6, 7, 4, 4], "skills": ["Marin Karin"], "question": "...Who the blazes do you think you are?", "a": "I feel bad about that", "b": "I'm ME!", "c": "I don't have to answer you", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Death", "trait": "Crisis Management", "inherits": "ailment", "item": "Mudoon"}, "Choronzon": {"stats": [5, 6, 1, 6, 7], "skills": ["Eiha"], "question": "Hey, sonny if somethin's been botherin' you. I'm willing to give you a listen.", "a": "My relationships...", "b": "My future...!", "c": "I have no worries", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Magician", "trait": "Bloodsucker", "inherits": "curse", "item": "Eiga Ring"}, "Dakini": {"stats": [6, 6, 1, 9, 3], "skills": ["Cleave"], "question": "Don't you think it's sad that slang and sayings can grow old and get outdated?", "a": "That is sad", "b": "I don't think so", "c": "That just proves you're old", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Empress", "trait": "Chained Technique", "inherits": "phys", "item": "Tempest Slash"}, "Decarabia": {"stats": [3, 3, 10, 6, 3], "skills": ["Agi"], "question": "Hey. So whaddya think when you think about the future?", "a": "An average level of happiness", "b": "Live fast, die young", "c": "I just want to enjoy the now", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Councillor", "trait": "Fire Lineage", "inherits": "fire", "item": "Maragion"}, "Dominion": {"stats": [5, 4, 5, 7, 4], "skills": ["Kouha"], "question": "That power, vow that you will use it in the name of our Father", "a": "I'll consider it", "b": "That's a bit much", "c": "I refuse", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Justice", "trait": "Bless Lineage", "inherits": "bless", "item": "Makougaon"}, "Eligor": {"stats": [6, 7, 6, 3, 3], "skills": ["Agi"], "question": "Y'know, if I'm gonna be killed, I'd rather be offed by some beautiful, classy woman", "a": "Sorry", "b": "You don't get to be picky", "c": "It's all the same", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Emperor", "trait": "Burning Touch", "inherits": "fire", "item": "Tarukaja"}, "Forneus": {"stats": [5, 6, 5, 4, 5], "skills": ["Psi"], "question": "What do ya usually eat?", "a": "Curry", "b": "Vegetables", "c": "Protein", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Magician", "trait": "Bloodshot Gaze", "inherits": "psy", "item": "Psiodyne"}, "Fuu-Ki": {"stats": [6, 8, 4, 3, 4], "skills": ["Garu"], "question": "A bad rep spreads like wildfire. If I were you, I'd quit all this nonsense. What's the point?", "a": "You're right", "b": "I don't care", "c": "I don't know any other way", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Star", "trait": "Focused Gaze", "inherits": "wind", "item": "Wind Boost"}, "Ganesha": {"stats": [4, 8, 6, 5, 2], "skills": ["Marin Karin"], "question": "I know when I'm gettin' all sweaty. I'm glistenin', ain't I?", "a": "Like a disco ball", "b": "Not at all", "c": "Why does that matter?", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Sun", "trait": "Life Focus", "inherits": "ailment", "item": "Rebellion"}, "Garuda": {"stats": [6, 8, 2, 3, 6], "skills": ["Garu"], "question": "What you thinking now?", "a": "I have homework tonight", "b": "I need a new cell phone", "c": "I want girls to like me", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Star", "trait": "Wind Lineage", "inherits": "wind", "item": "Garudyne"}, "Girimehkala": {"stats": [4, 7, 5, 5, 4], "skills": ["Marin Karin"], "question": "I coulda been a star...", "a": "A star?", "b": "That's never happening", "c": "Are you giving up?", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Moon", "trait": "Curse Lineage", "inherits": "ailment", "item": "Swift Strike"}, "Hanuman": {"stats": [7, 4, 3, 5, 6], "skills": ["Cleave"], "question": "What kinda fate do you think there is in this meetin' between me and you?", "a": "Fate brought us together", "b": "There is no such thing", "c": "I want to end this fate", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Strength", "trait": "Group Hypnosis", "inherits": "phys", "item": "Ruyi Jingu Bang"}, "High Pixie": {"stats": [5, 8, 2, 6, 4], "skills": ["Dia"], "question": "I'm inclined to turn you down, but if you still wish to speak, I will perhaps consider it", "a": "You have nothing I want", "b": "Are you bored?", "c": "That's horrible premise", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Fool", "trait": "Chained Technique", "inherits": "healing", "item": "Magaru"}, "Hua Po": {"stats": [3, 6, 6, 4, 6], "skills": ["Agi"], "question": "If your girlfriend asked if you were free to have dinner with her friends, what would you say?", "a": "Sure", "b": "I'm busy?", "c": "What are you talking about", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Hanged", "trait": "Burning Touch", "inherits": "fire", "item": "Agi Ring"}, "Incubus": {"stats": [6, 9, 4, 3, 3], "skills": ["Marin Karin"], "question": "They always give the guys katsudon! You got anything like that for me!?", "a": "Katsudon, coming right up", "b": "How about sushi...?", "c": "I have nothing for you", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Devil", "trait": "Bloodsucker", "inherits": "ailment", "item": "Dream Needle"}, "Inugami": {"stats": [4, 5, 8, 4, 4], "skills": ["Agi"], "question": "Me guessing you have power that me not have. But what is it...?", "a": "It's my intelligence", "b": "It's money", "c": "Girl power", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Hanged", "trait": "Foul Contagion", "inherits": "fire", "item": "Giant Slice"}, "Ippon-Datara": {"stats": [5, 4, 4, 8, 4], "skills": ["Cleave"], "question": "Hey. Why aren't you at school?", "a": "It's a school holiday", "b": "I don't feel like going", "c": "I actually finished school", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Hermit", "trait": "Heavyweight", "inherits": "phys", "item": "Sledgehammer"}, "Isis": {"stats": [4, 9, 4, 4, 4], "skills": ["Dia"], "question": "...I'm not going to go easy on you for doing something like this, you know...", "a": "I'm sorry", "b": "Prepare for the worst", "c": "How much do you want", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Priestess", "trait": "Recovery Lineage", "inherits": "healing", "item": "Kouga"}, "Jack Frost": {"stats": [6, 8, 4, 5, 2], "skills": ["Bufu"], "question": "Have you made an appointment, ho?", "a": "I have", "b": "That's not it", "c": "Just tell me what you know", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Magician", "trait": "Ice Lineage", "inherits": "ice", "item": "Frost Hood"}, "Kaiwan": {"stats": [3, 5, 9, 3, 5], "skills": ["Megido"], "question": "It'd prolly be a big downer if the birthday boy didn't show to his party, sooo...", "a": "Happy birthday", "b": "I had no idea", "c": "This'll be your deathday too", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Star", "trait": "Psy Lineage", "inherits": "almighty", "item": "Makajam"}, "Kali": {"stats": [3, 11, 4, 4, 3], "skills": ["Agi"], "question": "But I've been around the block, so I know--there's something else you want from me, isn't there?", "a": "Happy birthday", "b": "I had no idea", "c": "This'll be your deathday too", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Empress", "trait": "Relentlessness", "inherits": "fire", "item": "Null Psy"}, "Kelpie": {"stats": [7, 3, 5, 8, 2], "skills": ["Garu"], "question": "What you thinking now?", "a": "I have homework tonight", "b": "I need a new cell phone", "c": "I want girls to like me", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Strength", "trait": "Heavyweight", "inherits": "wind", "item": "Garu"}, "Kikuri-Hime": {"stats": [4, 7, 5, 4, 5], "skills": ["Dia"], "question": "What is irritating you so much?", "a": "Slow-ass cashiers", "b": "Egotistical women", "c": "I'm not irritated", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Priestess", "trait": "Support Lineage", "inherits": "healing", "item": "Energy Drop"}, "Kin-Ki": {"stats": [10, 2, 5, 4, 4], "skills": ["Cleave"], "question": "Me really want to eat something", "a": "Don't joke around", "b": "Just endure it", "c": "Want something delivered?", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Chariot", "trait": "Avenger", "inherits": "phys", "item": "Vajra Blast"}, "Kodama": {"stats": [10, 2, 4, 5, 4], "skills": ["Marin Karin"], "question": "When you eat curry, mister, what do you like to add?", "a": "Soy sauce", "b": "Worcestershire sauce", "c": "I don't add anything", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Star", "trait": "Chained Technique", "inherits": "ailment", "item": "Psi Ring"}, "Koppa Tengu": {"stats": [7, 4, 4, 4, 6], "skills": ["Garu"], "question": "...So uh, instead of killin' me, you started chattin' with me... You tryin' to get somethin' from me?", "a": "Yup", "b": "No... Nothing at all...", "c": "You're too self-conscious", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Temperance", "trait": "Focused Gaze", "inherits": "wind", "item": "Garu Ring"}, "Koropokkuru": {"stats": [4, 8, 7, 3, 3], "skills": ["Bufu"], "question": "Y'know, if I'm gonna be killed, I'd rather be offed by some beautiful, classy woman", "a": "Sorry", "b": "You don't get to be picky", "c": "It's all the same", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Hermit", "trait": "Foul Contagion", "inherits": "ice", "item": "Bufu"}, "Kumbhanda": {"stats": [4, 4, 4, 8, 5], "skills": ["Marin Karin"], "question": "Hey, if you got any medicine, lend me some. They're supposed ta work miracles, right...?", "a": "Are you OK?", "b": "What kind of medicine?", "c": "That won't change anything?", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Hermit", "trait": "Odd Immunity", "inherits": "ailment", "item": "Terror Claw"}, "Kushinada-Hime": {"stats": [5, 5, 5, 4, 6], "skills": ["Dia"], "question": "...Hey, there's no need for all this, right? Let's drop the drama and just go get something to eat. The thought has crossed your mind, hasn't it? Come on, where would you take me?", "a": "An expensive French restaurant", "b": "A busy ramen joint", "c": "A famous pancake place", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Lovers", "trait": "Recovery Lineage", "inherits": "healing", "item": "Diarama Ring"}, "Lamia": {"stats": [3, 8, 1, 7, 6], "skills": ["Agi"], "question": "I've been sending you serious don't speak to me vibes", "a": "I noticed", "b": "I didn't see any vibes", "c": "But we may never meet again...", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Empress", "trait": "Foul Contagion", "inherits": "fire", "item": "Rakukaja"}, "Lilim": {"stats": [3, 9, 4, 5, 4], "skills": ["Bufu"], "question": "Hey mister, if I grew up, what do you think the future me would've been like", "a": "A fashionable older woman", "b": "A weathly housewife", "c": "Living in the darkness", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Devil", "trait": "Freezing Follow-up", "inherits": "ice", "item": "Ice Boost"}, "Lilith": {"stats": [10, 4, 5, 4, 2], "skills": ["Megido"], "question": "You know, if I were to whip something up for you, what would you want?", "a": "Meat and potatoes", "b": "I don't need homemade food", "c": "Can you actually cook", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Moon", "trait": "Peerless Gaze", "inherits": "almighty", "item": "Null Nuke"}, "Makami": {"stats": [8, 6, 4, 2, 5], "skills": ["Frei"], "question": "You go back to your mother' arms. You need take nap now.", "a": "I'm not that young", "b": "I'm not sleepy yet", "c": "Mom will wait till I'm done", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Temperance", "trait": "Exquisite Technique", "inherits": "nuke", "item": "Frei"}, "Mandrake": {"stats": [11, 4, 4, 4, 2], "skills": ["Zio"], "question": "We'll just say you win. So can we stop this?", "a": "I feel bad", "b": "I don't agree with this", "c": "We can say you won", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Death", "trait": "Recovery Lineage", "inherits": "elec", "item": "Sukunda"}, "Melchizedek": {"stats": [1, 6, 5, 8, 5], "skills": ["Kouha"], "question": "Therefore, I cannot be destroyed. Desist from this pointlessness.?", "a": "What are you talking about?", "b": "That's absurd", "c": "You're lying", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Justice", "trait": "Deadly Plague", "inherits": "bless", "item": "Hamaon"}, "Mithras": {"stats": [1, 5, 4, 7, 8], "skills": ["Frei"], "question": "If I'd known things would end like this, I wish I had found the courage to ask that girl out...", "a": "Too late for regrets", "b": "You never had a chance", "c": "I'll make that girl happy", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Sun", "trait": "Exquisite Technique", "inherits": "nuke", "item": "Nuke Boost"}, "Mokoi": {"stats": [3, 11, 3, 3, 5], "skills": ["Marin Karin"], "question": "It's cliched, but we could chat about life... Ask each other things like what kind of girls we like...", "a": "I like older women", "b": "I like younger women", "c": "I like men", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Death", "trait": "Storm Born", "inherits": "ailment", "item": "Dekunda"}, "Moloch": {"stats": [2, 7, 9, 2, 5], "skills": ["Psi"], "question": "What's wrong with the way I look, huh?", "a": "You tempt people", "b": "You're ugly", "c": "Nothing's wrong", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Hanged", "trait": "Iron Immunity", "inherits": "fire", "item": "Agidyne Ring"}, "Mot": {"stats": [7, 8, 5, 1, 4], "skills": ["Marin Karin"], "question": "If you capture me, what you going to do to me?", "a": "Eat you in a hot pot", "b": "Take you to a taxidermist", "c": "You'll be my new stylish coat", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Death", "trait": "Peerless Gaze", "inherits": "ailment", "item": "Null Elec"}, "Mothman": {"stats": [4, 7, 4, 3, 7], "skills": ["Zio"], "question": "So why me in this situation right now? Why me at your mercy?", "a": "Times have changed", "b": "Humans are powerful", "c": "This is a difficult topic...", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Moon", "trait": "Shocking Follow-up", "inherits": "elec", "item": "Skull Cracker"}, "Naga": {"stats": [6, 2, 7, 3, 7], "skills": ["Zio"], "question": "As far as you're concerned, what kind of person was I to you?", "a": "My rival", "b": "Nobody, really", "c": "It doesn't matter", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Hermit", "trait": "Heavyweight", "inherits": "elec", "item": "Counter"}, "Narcissus": {"stats": [4, 5, 2, 5, 9], "skills": ["Marin Karin"], "question": "I mean, how does it feel to wave your gun at an enemy who's completely lost the will to fight?", "a": "It's not bad", "b": "...I could get used to it", "c": "It pains my heart...", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Lovers", "trait": "Life Focus", "inherits": "ailment", "item": "Dazzler"}, "Nebiros": {"stats": [5, 6, 3, 5, 6], "skills": ["Eiha"], "question": "The truth is... You're a good person, aren't you?", "a": "I get that a lot", "b": "Actually... I'm bad", "c": "Are you mocking me?", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Devil", "trait": "Psy Lineage", "inherits": "curse", "item": "Marin Karin"}, "Nekomata": {"stats": [4, 6, 3, 10, 2], "skills": ["Marin Karin"], "question": "I lost. Here I lay, at your feet, at your mercy. Just what do you want from me?", "a": "Give me something", "b": "Grovel before me", "c": "I don't know", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Magician", "trait": "Foul Contagion", "inherits": "ailment", "item": "Cat Punch Bazooka"}, "Norn": {"stats": [3, 9, 3, 4, 6], "skills": ["Megido"], "question": "Won't you just leave me be?", "a": "Are you busy?", "b": "I just couldn't", "c": "Is that reverse psychology?", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Fortune", "trait": "Focused Gaze", "inherits": "almighty", "item": "Recarm"}, "Nue": {"stats": [7, 6, 3, 5, 4], "skills": ["Eiha"], "question": "There something you want say to me, right?", "a": "Don't scratch the furniture?", "b": "I'll housebreak you", "c": "Let me touch your paws?", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Death", "trait": "Peerless Gaze", "inherits": "curse", "item": "Maeiha"}, "Obariyon": {"stats": [3, 6, 4, 3, 9], "skills": ["Cleave"], "question": "Aren't people as old as you s'posed to go dating, all the time? Can't you get some dates?", "a": "Right after this, kid", "b": "Such a rude little boy...", "c": "Dating's not important", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Fool", "trait": "Heavyweight", "inherits": "phys", "item": "Lucky Punch"}, "Oberon": {"stats": [6, 3, 4, 8, 4], "skills": ["Zio"], "question": "If your parents could see you now, I'm sure it would break their hearts...", "a": "You might be right...", "b": "This doesn't involve them", "c": "Actually, they'd rejoice", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Emperor", "trait": "Shocking Follow-up", "inherits": "elec", "item": "Heat Wave"}, "Oni": {"stats": [6, 6, 6, 3, 4], "skills": ["Cleave"], "question": "If yer gonna kill me, do me a solid and make it quick", "a": "Aren't you scared?", "b": "I'll have more fun first", "c": "Stop trying to act cool", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Strength", "trait": "Avenger", "inherits": "phys", "item": "Rampage"}, "Onmoraki": {"stats": [8, 5, 2, 3, 7], "skills": ["Eiha"], "question": "I'm tired of being a kid. Didn't you feel that way when you were little, too?", "a": "Sure did", "b": "Not really", "c": "I want to be a kid forever", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Moon", "trait": "Focused Gaze", "inherits": "curse", "item": "Eiha Ring"}, "Orobas": {"stats": [10, 3, 6, 4, 2], "skills": ["Agi"], "question": "You have no idea I was about to use my ultimate move", "a": "For real!?", "b": "That's worrying...", "c": "...Try me", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Hierophant", "trait": "Timid", "inherits": "fire", "item": "Rakunda"}, "Orthrus": {"stats": [3, 5, 10, 2, 5], "skills": ["Agi"], "question": "You given much thought, what if you go to place where you could die at any moment?", "a": "I've thought about it", "b": "I don't want kids", "c": "I'm not comfortable with this", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Hanged", "trait": "Burning Touch", "inherits": "fire", "item": "Agilao"}, "Ose": {"stats": [5, 6, 5, 2, 7], "skills": ["Marin Karin"], "question": "You're violatin' the weapons code or whatever, man", "a": "I didn't know", "b": "Not if no one finds out", "c": "Pretty cool, huh?", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Fool", "trait": "Avenger", "inherits": "ailment", "item": "Counterstrike"}, "Parvati": {"stats": [4, 4, 5, 4, 8], "skills": ["Psi"], "question": "Why have you decided to be more communicative with me?", "a": "Your looks", "b": "You seemed useful", "c": "No particular reason", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Lovers", "trait": "Exquisite Technique", "inherits": "psy", "item": "Null Ice"}, "Pisaca": {"stats": [6, 3, 4, 7, 5], "skills": ["Eiha"], "question": "I know when I'm gettin' all sweaty. I'm glistenin', ain't I?", "a": "Like a disco ball", "b": "Not at all", "c": "Why does that matter", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Death", "trait": "Odd Immunity", "inherits": "curse", "item": "Headhunter Ladle"}, "Pixie": {"stats": [3, 8, 4, 4, 6], "skills": ["Zio"], "question": "What do you think I should wear? I admit it, I wanna draw some attention to myself", "a": "High school uniform", "b": "Kimono", "c": "Don\u00e2\u20ac\u2122t wear anything", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Lovers", "trait": "Shocking Follow-up", "inherits": "elec", "item": "Zio Ring"}, "Power": {"stats": [2, 5, 3, 9, 6], "skills": ["Kouha"], "question": "To view me as an enemy is to incur our Father's wrath. Man's future rests in your hands", "a": "What are you trying to say?", "b": "You're exaggerating", "c": "That's pretty complicated", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Justice", "trait": "Self Hypnosis", "inherits": "bless", "item": "Bless Boost"}, "Queen Mab": {"stats": [3, 7, 4, 7, 4], "skills": ["Megido"], "question": "Ah, so I suppose you commit such extreme acts because you know you won't be punished harshly...", "a": "That's not true", "b": "Age doesn't matter", "c": "This isn't extreme", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Magician", "trait": "Shocking Follow-up", "inherits": "almighty", "item": "Masquerade Ribbon"}, "Rakshasa": {"stats": [5, 3, 6, 6, 5], "skills": ["Cleave"], "question": "...Um, why're you going' for me? Ain't there worse people out there? What kind of guys piss you off?", "a": "Slow walkers", "b": "Loud talkers...", "c": "Nobody", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Strength", "trait": "Chained Technique", "inherits": "phys", "item": "Regenerate 1"}, "Rangda": {"stats": [4, 4, 6, 7, 4], "skills": ["Eiha"], "question": "When I was young, I could make anyone back off - if they were smart enough - with just my glare", "a": "Fights are just luck", "b": "I'm just that good", "c": "You've grown old", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Magician", "trait": "Curse Lineage", "inherits": "curse", "item": "Maeiga"}, "Sandman": {"stats": [6, 8, 4, 4, 3], "skills": ["Garu"], "question": "I coulda been a star...", "a": "A star?", "b": "That's never happening", "c": "Are you giving up", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Magician", "trait": "Foul Contagion", "inherits": "wind", "item": "Dormina"}, "Sarasvati": {"stats": [4, 5, 4, 5, 7], "skills": ["Dia"], "question": "I wonder if us speaking together like this now means that we are somehow connected...", "a": "Eh, could be", "b": "No, I don't think so", "c": "It's what we call destiny", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Priestess", "trait": "Support Lineage", "inherits": "healing", "item": "Mediarama"}, "Scathach": {"stats": [5, 7, 6, 2, 5], "skills": ["Garu"], "question": "Ah, so I suppose you commit such extreme acts because you know you won't be punished harshly...", "a": "That's not true", "b": "Age doesn't matter", "c": "This isn't extreme", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Priestess", "trait": "Exquisite Technique", "inherits": "wind", "item": "Makarakarn"}, "Shiki-Ouji": {"stats": [5, 5, 7, 3, 5], "skills": ["Psi"], "question": "So me am going to haunt you for the rest of your life. Me always right behind you...", "a": "That would be troublesome", "b": "I could carry that weight", "c": "I wouldn't like that", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Chariot", "trait": "Psy Lineage", "inherits": "psy", "item": "Double Shot"}, "Silky": {"stats": [6, 7, 1, 4, 7], "skills": ["Dia"], "question": "...I'm not going to go easy on you for doing something like this, you know...", "a": "I'm sorry", "b": "Prepare for the worst", "c": "How much do you want", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Priestess", "trait": "Focused Gaze", "inherits": "healing", "item": "Silk Dress"}, "Skadi": {"stats": [6, 6, 3, 4, 6], "skills": ["Bufu"], "question": "They wear sleeveless shirts in the winter, right? What do you think about that, dearie?", "a": "I like it", "b": "They miss seasonal changes", "c": "I don't care", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Priestess", "trait": "Bloodshot Gaze", "inherits": "ice", "item": "Snow Queen Whip"}, "Slime": {"stats": [5, 7, 9, 3, 1], "skills": ["Eiha"], "question": "Me want to ask some recommendations, so me can at least imagine", "a": "Bread dipped in coffee", "b": "Ice cream off the carton lid", "c": "Hunger is the best spice", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Chariot", "trait": "Odd Immunity", "inherits": "curse", "item": "Tarunda"}, "Succubus": {"stats": [5, 8, 3, 1, 8], "skills": ["Eiha"], "question": "I'll go out with you just for today if there are no strings attached", "a": "If it pleases you", "b": "No strings attached", "c": "I've got enough on my plate...", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Moon", "trait": "Foul Contagion", "inherits": "curse", "item": "Brain Shot"}, "Sudama": {"stats": [4, 6, 4, 10, 1], "skills": ["Garu"], "question": "Where do babies come from?", "a": "Storks deliver them", "b": "Ask your parents", "c": "The love between two people", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Hermit", "trait": "Storm Born", "inherits": "psy", "item": "Mapsi"}, "Sui-Ki": {"stats": [4, 2, 7, 5, 7], "skills": ["Bufu"], "question": "So who're you tryin' to impress with that mask?", "a": "Nobody", "b": "Shuddup...", "c": "I'm actually still young...", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Moon", "trait": "Ice Lineage", "inherits": "ice", "item": "Bufula"}, "Take-Minakata": {"stats": [5, 6, 6, 4, 4], "skills": ["Zio"], "question": "You knocked me down, and now my goddamn watch is broken!", "a": "Sorry...", "b": "Not my problem", "c": "Don't lie", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Hanged", "trait": "Elec Lineage", "inherits": "elec", "item": "Zionga"}, "Thoth": {"stats": [6, 7, 3, 4, 5], "skills": ["Frei"], "question": "Why you fight and put yourself in harm's way?", "a": "I want to get stronger", "b": "Because I see an enemy", "c": "I don't actually know", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Emperor", "trait": "Exquisite Technique", "inherits": "nuke", "item": "Mafreila"}, "Titania": {"stats": [5, 10, 4, 3, 3], "skills": ["Frei"], "question": "I suppose this real world where you come from must be fairly boring", "a": "It's really boring", "b": "I'm always so busy there", "c": "It's better than here", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Empress", "trait": "Stagnant Aura", "inherits": "nuke", "item": "Freidyne"}, "Unicorn": {"stats": [5, 7, 7, 2, 4], "skills": ["Kouha"], "question": "You not worry you get in trouble if those groups hear what you are doing to me?", "a": "You're right", "b": "I don't care", "c": "You're not an animal", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Faith", "trait": "Bless Lineage", "inherits": "bless", "item": "Mahama"}, "Valkyrie": {"stats": [8, 4, 4, 5, 4], "skills": ["Cleave"], "question": "I insist you surrender yourself to the authorities", "a": "This is a misunderstanding", "b": "I don't have the time", "c": "You've got the wrong idea", "correct": "a", "arcana": "Strength", "trait": "Chained Technique", "inherits": "phys", "item": "Rising Slash"}, "Yaksini": {"stats": [5, 7, 5, 5, 3], "skills": ["Bufu"], "question": "I've heard that love can bloom anywhere, even on a battlefield. Don't you think that's possible?", "a": "Can it?", "b": "Definitely not", "c": "What are you saying?", "correct": "b", "arcana": "Empress", "trait": "Foul Contagion", "inherits": "ice", "item": "Hysterical Slap"}, "Yamata-no-Orochi": {"stats": [7, 5, 4, 3, 6], "skills": ["Bufu"], "question": "It look like you corner me... But how me know this not trick? How me know you really winning?", "a": "It doesn't change the facts?", "b": "I never tell lies", "c": "Don't try to escape reality?", "correct": "c", "arcana": "Judgement", "trait": "Freezing Follow-up", "inherits": "ice", "item": "Triple Down"}}